Guide to United States International University Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00135
Cubberley Education Library
United States International University (later merged with California School of Professional Psychology to become Alliant International University - San Diego; formerly California Western University, formerly Balboa University)
1947-1975
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00135
36 item(s)
Located in San Diego, CA. Founded in 1924 as Balboa Law College. Expanded to include other studies and changed name to Balboa University in 1945. Became California Western University in 1952. In 1966 became United States International University. Law school retained name California Western. Merged with California School of Professional Psychology in 2002 to become Alliant International University - San Diego.
California
- Balboa University, 1947-1953; 4 item(s) Bulletins for 1947/48-1949/50, 1952/53
- California Western University, 1952-1966; 19 item(s) Bulletins for 1952/53, 1955/56-1964/65
  - Report of the Department of Education of California Western University to the Committee on Accreditation of the State Board of Education Supporting application for receiving accreditation to issue the General Elementary Credential, September 1958; 1 item(s) Typescript report.
  - California Western University Course Schedule Point Loma Campus - Fall Semester 1958, 1 item(s) Typescript
  - California Western University: San Diego's Only Protestant Liberal Arts College, [1958]; 1 item(s) brochure
  - Report of California Western University to the Committee on Membership and Standards Western College Association and the Committee on Accreditation, California State Board of Education, November, 1959; 1 item(s) Typescript report
  - California Western University Summer Session, 1963-1964; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1963-1964
  - California Western University School of Law, 1964-1966; 2 item(s) Bulletin for 1964/65-1965/66
- United States International University, 1966-1975; 13 item(s)
  - United States International University California Western Division Graduate Programs, 1966-1967; 1 item(s) Bulletin for First College Arts and Sciences 1966/67
  - California Western University a Division of United States International University School of Education, 1966-1968; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1966/68
  - United States International University General Information, 1967-1968; 1 item(s) Pamphlet
  - United States International University - Elliott Campus Graduate School of Leadership and Human Behavior, 1968-69; 1 item(s) Typescript of Course Offerings for Spring Quarter 1968/69
  - United States International University - Elliott Campus College of Arts and Science, 1968-1969; 1 item(s) Typescript of Course Offerings for Spring Quarter 1968/69.
  - United States International University Graduate School of Business & Economics, 1968-1969; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1968/69
  - United States International University - Elliott Campus College of Arts and Sciences, 1968-1969; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1968/69
  - United States International University Summer Session, 1969-1970; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1969-1970
  - United States International University California Western School of Law, 1969-1975; 2 item(s) Bulletins for 1969/70, 1974/75
  - United States International University College of Arts and Sciences, 1971-1972; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1971/72
  - United States International University Undergraduate Bulletin, 1973-1974; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1973/74